Everyone seems to think that confidence
is a precursor to action,
but it's inverse.
Someone's like, "Oh,
just want to find the confidence to do
content." You're like,
"No, no, no.
That's not how this works." You do it
first, then you find the
confidence later.
The only way you get confident
is through doing it first, then
enduring it. The second thing
is eating shit is actually amazing because
every time
you do it,
there's a little bit of feedback.
So jujitsu, sorry.
Every time you make a mistake,
you get submitted.
But a submission isn't bad.
It's like your arm being straightened
or your wrist being bent, or an arm going
around your neck and someone squeezing.
But every time there's a signal to your
brain, "Shouldn't have done that.
That was a mistake." So next time
that happens, you go, "Cool.
I'm not going to put my hand in
that place." Then you go down a different
path of a
mistake or whatever.
But every time you get submitted,
there's no real harm that's
done to you. Your video bombs. Okay.
Watch it back. What was the issue?
Oh, a bit of feedback. People left here.
Why? Why was the click-through rate poor?
Why was this?
And it's only with those bits of content
that you can then start to
get the feedback necessary.
You don't have to do the same video twice.
You probably do the same idea twice.
But once you've done that video,
that piece of content, you've sent it.
Even if it's bombed, it's behind you now.
The next video you put out,
you're not going to be the same person.
You're going to be one video more
experienced, one video more
educated,
or the more comfortable in front of camera